Contact

geoffu@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/geoffunderwood-bsn-mba-81521565 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Cardiology Nursing ACLS

Geoff Underwood BSN, MBA

Nurse Manager at Mercy Health Anderson Dayton, Ohio

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Medical-Surgical, Nursing documentation and process management. Strong professional with a Master of Business Administration (MBA) focused in MBA with Healthcare Focus from Ohio University.

Experience

Mercy Health

Nurse Manager Noninvasive Cardiology, Inpatient Wound Care and Endoscopy

June 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months)

Anderson, Ohio

Manager of Non-Invasive Cardiology for the East. Anderson Hospital responsibilities include Echo, EKG, Stress Testing & Vascular Lab areas as well as the Cardiac Rehab department. Clermont Hospital responsibilities include Echo & Stress Testing areas, Vascular Lab & EKG departments as well as the Cardiac Rehab department. Manage Inpatient Wound Care at Anderson and Clermont Hospitals. Manage Endoscopy at Anderson Hospital.

Premier Health - Good Samaritan Hospital Nurse Manager December 2013 - June 2016 (2 years 7 months)

Responsible for the daily operations and management of a 35 bed unit that cares for the patient populations of Orthopedics, Spine, Gynecology, Oncology and general Med-Surg. Responsible for the management and development of 50+ staff members. Also manage and oversee the Orthopedic Services department.

Premier Health - Miami Valley Hospital 4 years 5 months

Associate Nurse Manager/Clinical Nurse Educator August 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 5 months) Associate Nurse Manager/Educator~ educating new staff and continuing education for the unit (i.e. practice changes, policy updates). Auditing, monitoring of staff performance and professional development of staff.

Registered Nurse August 2009 - July 2012 (3 years) Med-Surg Cardiology RN

Education

Ohio University

Master of Business Administration (MBA), MBA with Healthcare Focus \cdot (2013 - 2015)

Wright State University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2005 - 2009)